A Guide to the Episcopal Diocese of Southwestern Virginia 1905-1990
Digital Libraries and Archives, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Roanoke--St. John's--history (58) 1947-48 (Box-folder 80-24)
- St. Paul--Grace House Residence--Thomas A. Scott file (72A) 1947-48 (Box-folder 80-25)
- The Bishop's Plan (117A) 1947-48 (Box-folder 80-26)
- Boonsboro--Trinity 1948 (Box-folder 80-27)
- Clergy 1948 (Box-folder 80-28)
- Box 81 1948-50
- Gravatt, John James, Right Reverend, D.D.--former Rector of Trinity Church--Staunton 1948 (Box-folder 81-1)
- Gwathmey, D.L.--reports of the historiographer 1948 (Box-folder 81-2)
- Mountford, B. Frank, Captain--Secretary of the Church Army in the United States--Salem 1948 (Box-folder 81-3)
- Bedford--St. John's (9) 1948 (Box-folder 81-4)
- Blacksburg--Christ (14) 1948 (Box-folder 81-5)
- Bristol--Emmanuel (16) 1948 (Box-folder 81-6)
- Clifford--St. Mark's (23) 1948 (Box-folder 81-7)
- Ferrum--St. John's-in-the-mountains--history (30) 1948 (Box-folder 81-8)
- Forest--St. Stephen's (32) 1948 (Box-folder 81-9)
- Glasgow--St. John's (33) 1948 (Box-folder 81-10)
- Roanoke--St. Luke's--history including news reports (59) 1948 (Box-folder 81-11)
- St. Paul--Grace House--history (63) 1948 (Box-folder 81-12)
- "The Bishop's Plan" (118) 1948 (Box-folder 81-13)
- Church Pension Fund (121) 1948 (Box-folder 81-14)
- Church Pension Fund--re. individual clergymen--closed (121C) 1948 (Box-folder 81-15)
- Council--general (138) 1948 (Box-folder 81-16)
- Executive Board--Department of Christian Education (154) 1948 (Box-folder 81-17)
- Executive Board--Missions Department (158) 1948 (Box-folder 81-18)
- Field Department Pledges (163) 1948 (Box-folder 81-19)
- Executive Board--Finance Department (164) 1948 (Box-folder 81-20)
- Department of Religious Education--finances--Thomas A. Scott file (166) 1948 (Box-folder 81-21)
- Executive Board--general (168) 1948 (Box-folder 81-22)
- National Council--Treasurer--Thomas A. Scott file (206A) 1948 (Box-folder 81-23)
- #281 1948 (Box-folder 81-24)
- Evans Diocesan House--Roanoke--includes newsclippings and photographs 1948-49 (Box-folder 81-25)
- Morrill, E. Franc, Estate 1948-49 (Box-folder 81-26)
- Clifford--St. Mark's (23) 1948-49 (Box-folder 81-27)
- Pearisburg--Christ Church (51) 1948-49 (Box-folder 81-28)
- Staunton--Trinity--history (80) 1948-49 (Box-folder 81-29)
- Journal--publisher (175) 1948-49 (Box-folder 81-30)
- Laymen's League (189) 1948-49 (Box-folder 81-31)
- Roanoke--St. John's--history (58) 1948-50 (Box-folder 81-32)
- Virginia Episcopal School (223) 1948-50 (Box-folder 81-33)
- Accountant's Report 1949 (Box-folder 81-34)
- Brookneal 1949 (Box-folder 81-35)
- Clergy 1949 (Box-folder 81-36)
- General Convention--transportation, etc. 1949 (Box-folder 81-37)
- General Convention--commission on business methods in church schools, hospitals, and other institutions 1949 (Box-folder 81-38)
- Council--minutes 1949 (Box-folder 81-39)
- National Council--Treasurer--Thomas A. Scott file--Domestic and Foreign Missionary Society receipts 1949 (Box-folder 81-40)
- Vestries 1949 (Box-folder 81-41)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas (2) 1949 (Box-folder 81-42)
- Altavista--St. Peter's (4) 1949 (Box-folder 81-43)
- Amherst--Ascension (5) 1949 (Box-folder 81-44)
- Amherst--St. Paul's Mission (6) 1949 (Box-folder 81-45)
- Arrington--Trinity (8) 1949 (Box-folder 81-46)
- Bedford--St. James (9); Bedford--St. Philip's (10) 1949 (Box-folder 81-47)
- Big Island--St. Thomas (11) 1949 (Box-folder 81-48)
- Big Stone Gap--Christ Church (12) 1949 (Box-folder 81-49)
- Blacksburg--Christ Church (13) 1949 (Box-folder 81-50)
- Bristol--Emmanuel--includes undated article regarding Reverend Maurice Henry Hopson (16) 1949 (Box-folder 81-51)
- Buchanan--Grace (17) 1949 (Box-folder 81-52)
- Callaway--St. Peter's (20) 1949 (Box-folder 81-53)
- Clifton Forge--St. Andrew's (24) 1949 (Box-folder 81-54)
- Covington--Emmanuel (25) 1949 (Box-folder 81-55)
- Dante--St. Mark's (27) 1949 (Box-folder 81-56)
- Eagle Rock--Emmanuel (28) 1949 (Box-folder 81-57)
- Ferrum--St. John's (30) 1949 (Box-folder 81-58)
- Fincastle--St. Mark's (31) 1949 (Box-folder 81-59)
- Forest--St. Stephen's (32) 1949 (Box-folder 81-60)
- Glade Spring--Grace--re. deconsecration, etc (32A) 1949 (Box-folder 81-61)
- Glasgow--St. John's (33) 1949 (Box-folder 81-62)
- Lexington--R.E. Lee Memorial (37) 1949 (Box-folder 81-63)
- Lexington--R.E. Lee Memorial (37) 1949 (Box-folder 81-64)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (38) 1949 (Box-folder 81-65)
- Lynchburg--St. John's (41) 1949 (Box-folder 81-66)
- Lynchburg--St. John's (41) 1949 (Box-folder 81-67)
- Lynchburg--St. Paul's (42) 1949 (Box-folder 81-68)
- Martinsville--St. Paul's (46) 1949 (Box-folder 81-69)
- Massies Mill--Grace (47) 1949 (Box-folder 81-70)
- Nora--St. Stephen's (48) 1949 (Box-folder 81-71)
- Norton--All Saints (49) 1949 (Box-folder 81-72)
- Norton--All Saints (49) 1949 (Box-folder 81-73)
- Norwood--Christ Church (50) 1949 (Box-folder 81-74)
- Pedlar Mills--St. Luke's (52) 1949 (Box-folder 81-75)
- Pocahontas--Christ Church (53) 1949 (Box-folder 81-76)
- Pulaski--Christ (54) 1949 (Box-folder 81-77)
- Radford--Grace (55) 1949 (Box-folder 81-78)
- Roanoke--Christ Church (57) 1949 (Box-folder 81-79)
- Roanoke--St. John's (58) 1949 (Box-folder 81-80)
- Roanoke--St. Luke's (59) 1949 (Box-folder 81-81)
- Roanoke--St. Peter's (60) 1949 (Box-folder 81-82)
- St. Paul--Grace House-on-the-mountain (63) 1949 (Box-folder 81-83)
- St. Paul--Honey Branch (64) 1949 (Box-folder 81-84)
- Saltville--St. Paul's (66) 1949 (Box-folder 81-85)
- Roanoke--St. Peter's (70) 1949 (Box-folder 81-86)
- Staunton--Trinity (71) 1949 (Box-folder 81-87)
- Staunton--RFD #1--Folly Mills--Good Shepherd (72) 1949 (Box-folder 81-88)
- Folly Mills--Good Shepherd (72) 1949 (Box-folder 81-89)
- Waynesboro--St. John's--history (76) 1949 (Box-folder 81-90)
- Waynesboro--St. John's (76) 1949 (Box-folder 81-91)
- Wytheville--St. John's (77) 1949 (Box-folder 81-92)
- Wytheville--St. John's--history (77) 1949 (Box-folder 81-93)
- Bishop's Plan (109) 1949 (Box-folder 81-94)
- Church Pension Fund (121) 1949 (Box-folder 81-95)
- Clergy Conference (124) 1949 (Box-folder 81-96)
- Council--elections and credentials (130) 1949 (Box-folder 81-97)
- Council--general (131) 1949 (Box-folder 81-98)
- Council--reports (138) 1949 (Box-folder 81-99)
- Box 82 1949-51
- Council--Secretary (141) 1949 (Box-folder 82-1)
- Executive Board--Department of Christian Education (154) 1949 (Box-folder 82-2)
- Elliot Addressing Machine (155A) 1949 (Box-folder 82-3)
- Executive Board--Department of Finance (157) 1949 (Box-folder 82-4)
- Executive Board--Department of Promotion (159) 1949 (Box-folder 82-5)
- Department of Religious Education--finances--Thomas A. Scott file (166) 1949 (Box-folder 82-6)
- General Convention--Thomas A. Scott (174A) 1949 (Box-folder 82-7)
- Blacksburg--Christ (14) 1949-50 (Box-folder 82-8)
- Cambria--RFD--Emmanuel--"High Top" (21) 1949-50 (Box-folder 82-9)
- Christiansburg--St. Thomas (22) 1949-50 (Box-folder 82-10)
- Hot Springs--St. Luke's (34) 1949-50 (Box-folder 82-11)
- Lynchburg--Grace Memorial (39) 1949-50 (Box-folder 82-12)
- Madison Heights--Emmanuel (43) 1949-50 (Box-folder 82-13)
- Marion--Christ Church (44) 1949-50 (Box-folder 82-14)
- Martinsville--Christ Church (45) 1949-50 (Box-folder 82-15)
- Richlands--Trinity (56) 1949-50 (Box-folder 82-16)
- Rocky Mount-Trinity--history (62) 1949-50 (Box-folder 82-17)
- Schuyler--Christ Church (67) 1949-51 (Box-folder 82-18)
- Accountant's Reports 1950 (Box-folder 82-19)
- Clergy 1950 (Box-folder 82-20)
- Diocesan Calendar 1950 (Box-folder 82-21)
- Field Department pledges for 1950 1950 (Box-folder 82-22)
- Gladys--Christ (Campbell County) 1950 (Box-folder 82-23)
- History of the Episcopal Church 1950 (Box-folder 82-24)
- Jett, Robert Carter, Right Reverend, D.D.--first Bishop of the Diocese of Southwestern Virginia 1950 (Box-folder 82-25)
- Laymen--training and meetings 1950 (Box-folder 82-26)
- Morrill, E. Franc, Estate 1950 (Box-folder 82-27)
- St. Paul--Honey Branch and Dante--history 1950 (Box-folder 82-28)
- St. Paul RFD--Sandy Ridge Mission--deeds and correspondence relating thereto 1950 (Box-folder 82-29)
- Staunton--RFD #1--Folly Mills--Good Shepherd 1950 (Box-folder 82-30)
- Vestries 1950 (Box-folder 82-31)
- Virginia Theological Seminary--Committee on honorary de- grees (1950) 1950 (Box-folder 82-32)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas (2) 1950 (Box-folder 82-33)
- Altavista--St. Peter's (4) 1950 (Box-folder 82-34)
- Altavista--St. Peter's (4) 1950 (Box-folder 82-35)
- Amherst--Ascension (5) 1950 (Box-folder 82-36)
- Amherst--St. Paul's Mission (6) 1950 (Box-folder 82-37)
- Amherst--St. Paul's Mission--history including Christmas 1949 (6) 1950 (Box-folder 82-38)
- Arrington--Trinity (8) 1950 (Box-folder 82-39)
- Bedford--St. James (9) 1950 (Box-folder 82-40)
- Bedford--St. Philip's (10) 1950 (Box-folder 82-41)
- Big Stone Gap--Christ Church (12) 1950 (Box-folder 82-42)
- Blacksburg--Christ Church (13) 1950 (Box-folder 82-43)
- Bluefield--St. Mary's (14) 1950 (Box-folder 82-44)
- Bluefield--St. Mary's (14) 1950 (Box-folder 82-45)
- Bristol--Emmanuel (16) 1950 (Box-folder 82-46)
- Buena Vista--Christ Church (19) 1950 (Box-folder 82-47)
- Callaway--St. Peter's (20) 1950 (Box-folder 82-48)
- Clifford--St. Mark's (23) 1950 (Box-folder 82-49)
- Clifton Forge--St. Andrew's (24) 1950 (Box-folder 82-50)
- Covington--Emmanuel (25) 1950 (Box-folder 82-51)
- Covington--Emmanuel (25) 1950 (Box-folder 82-52)
- Dante--St. Mark's (27) 1950 (Box-folder 82-53)
- Evington--Good Shepherd (29) 1950 (Box-folder 82-54)
- Ferrum--St. John's (30) 1950 (Box-folder 82-55)
- Forest--St. Stephen's (32) 1950 (Box-folder 82-56)
- Glasgow--St. John's (33) 1950 (Box-folder 82-57)
- Glasgow--St. John's--includes undated newsclipping regard- ing Reverend S. Janney Hutton's resignation (33) 1950 (Box-folder 82-58)
- Lexington--R.E. Lee Memorial (37) 1950 (Box-folder 82-59)
- Lexington--R.E. Lee Memorial (37) 1950 (Box-folder 82-60)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (38) 1950 (Box-folder 82-61)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (39) 1950 (Box-folder 82-62)
- Lynchburg--St. John's (41) 1950 (Box-folder 82-63)
- Martinsville--St. Paul's (46) 1950 (Box-folder 82-64)
- Massies Mill--Grace (47) 1950 (Box-folder 82-65)
- Nora--St. Stephen's (48) 1950 (Box-folder 82-66)
- Norton--All Saints (49) 1950 (Box-folder 82-67)
- Pearisburg--Christ Church (51) 1950 (Box-folder 82-68)
- Pearisburg--Christ (51) 1950 (Box-folder 82-69)
- Pocahontas--Christ Church (53) 1950 (Box-folder 82-70)
- Pulaski--Christ--history (54) 1950 (Box-folder 82-71)
- Richlands--Trinity--history (56) 1950 (Box-folder 82-72)
- Roanoke--St. James (57A) 1950 (Box-folder 82-73)
- Roanoke--St. James--history (57A) 1950 (Box-folder 82-74)
- Roanoke--St. John's (58) 1950 (Box-folder 82-75)
- St. Paul--Grace House-on-the-mountain (63) 1950 (Box-folder 82-76)
- St. Paul--Honey Branch (64) 1950 (Box-folder 82-77)
- Salem--St. Paul's--history (65) 1950 (Box-folder 82-78)
- Roanoke--Christ (67) 1950 (Box-folder 82-79)
- Roanoke--St. Peter's (70) 1950 (Box-folder 82-80)
- Staunton--Emmanuel (70) 1950 (Box-folder 82-81)
- Staunton--Trinity (71) 1950 (Box-folder 82-82)
- Waynesboro--St. John's--history (76) 1950 (Box-folder 82-83)
- Wytheville--St. John's (77) 1950 (Box-folder 82-84)
- Box 83 1950-51
- Bishop's Plan (109) 1950 (Box-folder 83-1)
- College Work (119) 1950 (Box-folder 83-2)
- Church Pension Fund (121) 1950 (Box-folder 83-3)
- Council--elections and credentials (130) 1950 (Box-folder 83-4)
- Council--minutes (134) 1950 (Box-folder 83-5)
- Council--program (137) 1950 (Box-folder 83-6)
- Council--reports (138) 1950 (Box-folder 83-7)
- Council--Secretary (141) 1950 (Box-folder 83-8)
- Executive Board--Department of Christian Education (154) 1950 (Box-folder 83-9)
- Executive Board--Department of Finance (157) 1950 (Box-folder 83-10)
- Executive Board--Department of Promotion (159) 1950 (Box-folder 83-11)
- Executive Board--general (160) 1950 (Box-folder 83-12)
- Department of Religious Education--finances--Thomas A. Scott file (166) 1950 (Box-folder 83-13)
- Bishop Jett Memorial (171A) 1950 (Box-folder 83-14)
- Journal--publisher (175) 1950 (Box-folder 83-15)
- Lambeth Conference (176) 1950 (Box-folder 83-16)
- Permanent Laymen's League (178) 1950 (Box-folder 83-17)
- Laymen's League (189) 1950 (Box-folder 83-18)
- St. Paul's Polytechnic Institute (210) 1950 (Box-folder 83-19)
- Women Workers--permanent--prospective (230) 1950 (Box-folder 83-20)
- National Council of the Churches of Christ in the U.S.A. 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-21)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas--history including photographs (2) 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-22)
- Bedford--St. John's (9) 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-23)
- Big Island--St. Thomas (11) 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-24)
- Clifford--St. Mark's (23) 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-25)
- Clifton Forge--St. Andrew's (24) 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-26)
- Ivanhoe--St. Andrew's (35) 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-27)
- Gladys--Christ Church (39) 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-28)
- Lynchburg--St. Paul's (42) 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-29)
- Norwood--Christ Church (50) 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-30)
- Pedlar Mills--St. Luke (52) 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-31)
- Pulaski--Christ (54) 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-32)
- Radford--Grace--includes newsclipping 1951 regarding Dr. Homer Howard, nominated for president of Radford College (55) 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-33)
- Roanoke--Christ Church (57) 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-34)
- Roanoke--St. John's--history (58) 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-35)
- Roanoke--St. Luke's--history (59) 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-36)
- Roanoke--St. Peter's (60) 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-37)
- Splashdam--Mission--Good Shepherd (69) 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-38)
- Tazewell--Stras Memorial (75) 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-39)
- Waynesboro--St. John's (76) 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-40)
- Stuart Hall (216) 1950-51 (Box-folder 83-41)
- Accountant's Report 1951 (Box-folder 83-42)
- Barnwell, Carlton, Reverend, D.D. 1951 (Box-folder 83-43)
- Clergy 1951 (Box-folder 83-44)
- Clergy--elections and credentials 1951 (Box-folder 83-45)
- Council--reports 1951 (Box-folder 83-46)
- Council--Secretary 1951 (Box-folder 83-47)
- Diocesan Council 1951 (Box-folder 83-48)
- Field Department pledges for 1951 and pledges for advance fund for Roanoke--St. James Church (1951) 1951 (Box-folder 83-49)
- Gwathmey, D.L.--regarding 30th anniversary as rector of St. John's Church--Wytheville 1951 (Box-folder 83-50)
- Journal--publisher 1951 (Box-folder 83-51)
- Laymen--training and meetings 1951 (Box-folder 83-52)
- Mayer, Alice Wilcox, Deaconess 1951 (Box-folder 83-53)
- Morrill, E. Franc, Estate 1951 (Box-folder 83-54)
- Rogers, Floyd, Reverend--founder of Boys' Home at Covington 1951 (Box-folder 83-55)
- Box 84 1951-53
- Vestries 1951 (Box-folder 84-1)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas (2) 1951 (Box-folder 84-2)
- Altavista--St. Peter's (4) 1951 (Box-folder 84-3)
- Altavista--St. Peter's (4) 1951 (Box-folder 84-4)
- Amherst--Ascension (5) 1951 (Box-folder 84-5)
- Amherst--St. Paul's Mission (6) 1951 (Box-folder 84-6)
- Arrington--Trinity (8) 1951 (Box-folder 84-7)
- Bedford--St. Philip's (10) 1951 (Box-folder 84-8)
- Big Stone Gap--Christ Church (12) 1951 (Box-folder 84-9)
- Blacksburg--Christ Church (13) 1951 (Box-folder 84-10)
- Blacksburg--Christ (14) 1951 (Box-folder 84-11)
- Bluefield--St. Mary's (15) 1951 (Box-folder 84-12)
- Bristol--Emmanuel (16) 1951 (Box-folder 84-13)
- Bristol--Emmanuel (16) 1951 (Box-folder 84-14)
- Buena Vista--Christ Church--includes undated newsclipping regarding repairs to church (19) 1951 (Box-folder 84-15)
- Callaway--St. Peter's (20) 1951 (Box-folder 84-16)
- Callaway--St. Peter's--history (20) 1951 (Box-folder 84-17)
- Covington--Emmanuel (25) 1951 (Box-folder 84-18)
- Dante--St. Mark's (27) 1951 (Box-folder 84-19)
- Evington--Good Shepherd (29) 1951 (Box-folder 84-20)
- Ferrum--St. John's (30) 1951 (Box-folder 84-21)
- Forest--St. Stephen's (32) 1951 (Box-folder 84-22)
- Glasgow--St. John's (33) 1951 (Box-folder 84-23)
- Hot Springs--St. Luke's (34) 1951 (Box-folder 84-24)
- Lexington--R.E. Lee Memorial (37) 1951 (Box-folder 84-25)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (38) 1951 (Box-folder 84-26)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (39) 1951 (Box-folder 84-27)
- Marion--Christ Church (44) 1951 (Box-folder 84-28)
- Martinsville--Christ Church (45) 1951 (Box-folder 84-29)
- Martinsville--St. Paul's (46) 1951 (Box-folder 84-30)
- Nora--St. Stephen's (48) 1951 (Box-folder 84-31)
- Norton--All Saints (49) 1951 (Box-folder 84-32)
- Pearisburg--Christ Church (51) 1951 (Box-folder 84-33)
- Pulaski--Christ--history (54) 1951 (Box-folder 84-34)
- Richlands--Trinity (56) 1951 (Box-folder 84-35)
- Roanoke--Christ (57) 1951 (Box-folder 84-36)
- Roanoke--St. James (57A) 1951 (Box-folder 84-37)
- Roanoke--St. James--history with photographs and news clippings (57A) 1951 (Box-folder 84-38)
- Roanoke--St. John's (58) 1951 (Box-folder 84-39)
- Roanoke--St. Peter's (60) 1951 (Box-folder 84-40)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity (62) 1951 (Box-folder 84-41)
- St. Paul--Grace House--history with news clippings (63) 1951 (Box-folder 84-42)
- St. Paul--Grace House-on-the-mountain (63) 1951 (Box-folder 84-43)
- St. Paul--Honey Branch (64) 1951 (Box-folder 84-44)
- Salem--St. Paul's (65) 1951 (Box-folder 84-45)
- Salem--St. Paul's--history (65) 1951 (Box-folder 84-46)
- Staunton--Emmanuel (70) 1951 (Box-folder 84-47)
- Staunton--Trinity (71) 1951 (Box-folder 84-48)
- Staunton--RFD #1--Trinity Church (71); Staunton--RFD #1--Good Shepherd at Folly Mills (72) 1951 (Box-folder 84-49)
- Folly Mills--Good Shepherd (72) 1951 (Box-folder 84-50)
- Tazewell--Stras Memorial--history (75) 1951 (Box-folder 84-51)
- Warm Springs--Christ Church--history (75A) 1951 (Box-folder 84-52)
- Wytheville--St. John's (77) 1951 (Box-folder 84-53)
- Wytheville--St. John's--history (77) 1951 (Box-folder 84-54)
- Yards--Mission (78) 1951 (Box-folder 84-55)
- Bishop's Plan (109) 1951 (Box-folder 84-56)
- Church Pension Fund (121) 1951 (Box-folder 84-57)
- Council--Secretary (134) 1951 (Box-folder 84-58)
- Executive Board--Department of Finance (157) 1951 (Box-folder 84-59)
- Executive Board--Department of Promotion (Folder 1 of 2, 159) 1951 (Box-folder 84-60)
- Executive Board--Department of Promotion (Folder 2 of 2, 159) 1951 (Box-folder 84-61)
- Executive Board--general (160) 1951 (Box-folder 84-62)
- Executive Board--Finance Department (164) 1951 (Box-folder 84-63)
- Department of Religious Education--finances--Thomas A. Scott file (166) 1951 (Box-folder 84-64)
- Bishop Jett--memorial service and memorial (171A) 1951 (Box-folder 84-65)
- Stuart Hall (216) 1951 (Box-folder 84-66)
- Treasurer of Diocese (218) 1951 (Box-folder 84-67)
- Women Workers--permanent--prospective (230) 1951 (Box-folder 84-68)
- Biographies 1951-52 (Box-folder 84-69)
- Wytheville--St. John's--history--newspaper clippings 1951-52 (Box-folder 84-70)
- Bedford--St. James (9) 1951-52 (Box-folder 84-71)
- Bedford--St. Philip's--history (10) 1951-52 (Box-folder 84-72)
- Buena Vista--Christ Church (19) 1951-52 (Box-folder 84-73)
- Christiansburg--St. Thomas (22) 1951-52 (Box-folder 84-74)
- Hot Springs--St. Luke's (34) 1951-52 (Box-folder 84-75)
- Lynchburg--Grace Memorial (39) 1951-52 (Box-folder 84-76)
- Martinsville--St. Paul's (46) 1951-52 (Box-folder 84-77)
- Massies Mill--Grace (47) 1951-52 (Box-folder 84-78)
- Pocahontas--Christ Church (53) 1951-52 (Box-folder 84-79)
- Richlands--Trinity--history (56) 1951-52 (Box-folder 84-80)
- Roanoke--St. Peter's--history (60) 1951-52 (Box-folder 84-81)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity--history (62) 1951-52 (Box-folder 84-82)
- Saltville--St. Paul's (66) 1951-52 (Box-folder 84-83)
- Staunton--RFD #1--Folly Mills--Good Shepherd (72) 1951-52 (Box-folder 84-84)
- Staunton--RFD #4--Verona (73) 1951-52 (Box-folder 84-85)
- Evans Diocesan House--Roanoke 1951-53 (Box-folder 84-86)
- Box 85 1952
- Accountant's Report 1952 (Box-folder 85-1)
- Brookneal--Christ Church 1952 (Box-folder 85-2)
- Clergy 1952 (Box-folder 85-3)
- Clergy Prospects 1952 (Box-folder 85-4)
- General Convention 1952 (Box-folder 85-5)
- General Convention--hotels, transportation, etc. 1952 (Box-folder 85-6)
- General Convention--Thomas A. Scott--Deputy 1952 (Box-folder 85-7)
- Council 1952 (Box-folder 85-8)
- Council--minutes 1952 (Box-folder 85-9)
- Council--reports 1952 (Box-folder 85-10)
- Council--Secretary 1952 (Box-folder 85-11)
- Field Department Pledges 1952 (Box-folder 85-12)
- Journal--Publisher 1952 (Box-folder 85-13)
- Laymen--training and meetings 1952 (Box-folder 85-14)
- Morrill, E. Franc--Estate 1952 (Box-folder 85-15)
- Department of Promotion--requisitions for materials 1952 (Box-folder 85-16)
- Trinity and St. Stephen's Churches (1952) 1952 (Box-folder 85-17)
- Vestries 1952 (Box-folder 85-18)
- Altavista--St. Peter's (4) 1952 (Box-folder 85-19)
- Amherst--Ascension (5) 1952 (Box-folder 85-20)
- Amherst--Ascension (5) 1952 (Box-folder 85-21)
- Amherst--St. Paul's Mission--history (6) 1952 (Box-folder 85-22)
- Arrington--Trinity (8) 1952 (Box-folder 85-23)
- Bedford--St. Philip's (10) 1952 (Box-folder 85-24)
- Big Stone Gap--Christ Church (12) 1952 (Box-folder 85-25)
- Blacksburg--Christ (14) 1952 (Box-folder 85-26)
- Bluefield--St. Mary's (14) 1952 (Box-folder 85-27)
- Callaway--St. Peter's (20) 1952 (Box-folder 85-28)
- Cambria--RFD--Emmanuel--"High Top" (21) 1952 (Box-folder 85-29)
- Covington--Emmanuel (25) 1952 (Box-folder 85-30)
- Eagle Rock--Emmanuel (28) 1952 (Box-folder 85-31)
- Ferrum--St. John's (30) 1952 (Box-folder 85-32)
- Ferrum--St. John's-in-the-mountains--history (30) 1952 (Box-folder 85-33)
- Forest--St. Stephen's (32) 1952 (Box-folder 85-34)
- Glasgow--St. John's (33) 1952 (Box-folder 85-35)
- Lexington--R.E. Lee Memorial (37) 1952 (Box-folder 85-36)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (38) 1952 (Box-folder 85-37)
- Lynchburg--St. John's (41) 1952 (Box-folder 85-38)
- Lynchburg--St. John's (41) 1952 (Box-folder 85-39)
- Marion--Christ Church (44) 1952 (Box-folder 85-40)
- Martinsville--Christ Church (45) 1952 (Box-folder 85-41)
- Nora--St. Stephen's (48) 1952 (Box-folder 85-42)
- Pearisburg--Christ (51) 1952 (Box-folder 85-43)
- Pearisburg--Christ Church (51) 1952 (Box-folder 85-44)
- Pedlar Mills--St. Luke's (52) 1952 (Box-folder 85-45)
- Pulaski--Christ--history (54) 1952 (Box-folder 85-46)
- Richlands--Trinity (56) 1952 (Box-folder 85-47)
- Roanoke--Christ (57) 1952 (Box-folder 85-48)
- Roanoke--St. James (57A) 1952 (Box-folder 85-49)
- Roanoke--St. James--history (57A) 1952 (Box-folder 85-50)
- Roanoke--St. John's--history--news clippings (58) 1952 (Box-folder 85-51)
- Roanoke--St. Luke's--history including undated newsclippings (59) 1952 (Box-folder 85-52)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity (62) 1952 (Box-folder 85-53)
- St. Paul--Grace House-on-the-mountain (63) 1952 (Box-folder 85-54)
- St. Paul--Honey Branch/Dante--history (64) 1952 (Box-folder 85-55)
- Salem--St. Paul's--history (65) 1952 (Box-folder 85-56)
- Splashdam Mission--Good Shepherd (69) 1952 (Box-folder 85-57)
- Splashdam--Mission--history (69) 1952 (Box-folder 85-58)
- Staunton--Emmanuel (70) 1952 (Box-folder 85-59)
- Staunton--Trinity (71) 1952 (Box-folder 85-60)
- Staunton--Trinity--history (71) 1952 (Box-folder 85-61)
- Emmanuel Chapel--Verona [Staunton RFD]--history (73) 1952 (Box-folder 85-62)
- Waynesboro--St. John's (76) 1952 (Box-folder 85-63)
- Waynesboro--St. John's--history including information regarding Reverend Kenneth H. Anthony (76) 1952 (Box-folder 85-64)
- Wytheville--St. John's (77) 1952 (Box-folder 85-65)
- Bishop's Plan (109) 1952 (Box-folder 85-66)
- Church Pension Fund (121) 1952 (Box-folder 85-67)
- Executive Board--Department of Finance (157) 1952 (Box-folder 85-68)
- Executive Board--Department of Finance (157) 1952 (Box-folder 85-69)
- Executive Board--Department of Promotion (159) 1952 (Box-folder 85-70)
- Executive Board--Department of Promotion (159) 1952 (Box-folder 85-71)